chingoracle.com 2016-11-19

# Privacy | Chingoracle.com

This statement describes the privacy practices of Lucini & Lucini Communications Limited in connection with this website, (the “Website”)

This statement relates only to the processing of personal data performed through the Website and not with reference to other websites possibly accessed by using the links that appear on the Website for which Lucini & Lucini Communications Limited shall not be in any case responsible.

## DATA CONTROLLER

The Website is operated by Lucini & Lucini Communications Limited, (company registration no. 505254), registered in Ireland, having its registered office at 19 Fitzwilliam Place, Dublin 2, Ireland (the “Data Controller”).

For any contact and information, users are invited to write to the Data Controller at the mentioned address or sending an e-mail to [privacy@lucinilucini.com](mailto:privacy@lucinilucini.com).

## PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED

For users to avail of certain subscription services on the Website (such as Astrochat, dating under the star, daily horoscope by email), (the “Services”), they will need to register and provide certain personal data. Examples of personal data collected for purposes of providing the Services are: user’s name, e-mail address, gender, place and date of birth, country, profession, education level, interests, pets and existence of children.

In order to render the Services not all the above mentioned personal data are required. The required personal data is expressly indicated on the Website.

For the purposes of better safeguarding privacy, users’ surname is not requested by the Website.

If you are merely visiting public areas of the Website, the Data Controller does not collect any personal data about users. However, the Data Controller may automatically collect information about users’ visits, such as browsing patterns. Information collected in this way does not reveal users’ contact details or any type of personal data. This anonymised information is only used in aggregate form to analyse, manage and develop the Website and is not linked to any individual.

Personal data will be processed by the Data Controller and stored on servers situated in Europe or outside the European Economic Area. By users submitting their personal data, they agree to the storing and processing of their personal data as outlined in this statement.

## PURPOSES OF PERSONAL DATA

The personal data provided by users are processed for the following purposes:

1\. to comply with duties imposed by laws and regulations, as well as lawful requests issued by the competent authorities/bodies of supervision and control including the police and government authorities; 

2\. to fulfil the request sent by the user to the Website and/or to subscribe to the Website and to receive the Services. In particular, the processing of personal data allows: (i) the users to actively participate to the on-line community of Chingoracle to manage a public profile and interact with other users by means of the meeting and/or entertainment services offered; (ii) the Data Controller to perform the requests and/or respond to queries made by the user and/or to periodically send to the user information and communications (such as communications relating to horoscopes, biorhythms or others subscribed services) depending on the selected Service; (iii) manage the user’s profile in order to personalise the Services; (iv) customise the content and information the user receives and the Data Controller’s communications with the user; 

3\. for profiling purposes and to periodically send to the users, via e-mail, communications for direct marketing purposes relating to products or services rendered by the Data Controller and/or other companies, operating in several industries, or invitations to participate in market and research surveys regarding the Services rendered by the Data Controller or other services rendered by other companies.

## DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL DATA TO THIRD PARTIES

The Data Controller may have the need to access and disclose your personal data to third parties pertaining to one of the following categories: authorities or surveillance bodies including lawful requests from government authorities or requests by the police investigating suspected illegal activities; to third parties regarding the operation, maintenance, development and improvement of the Website and the IT systems of the Data Controller (including analytics and search engine providers); to companies in the Data Controller’s Group; to selected third parties including business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of the Services as well as companies that provide insurance services; to comply with any legal obligation; to protect the Data Controller or other Website users; to third parties if a complaint arises concerning use of the Website by a user and that use is deemed by the Data Controller to be inconsistent with its terms and conditions; in order to enforce or apply the Website’s terms and conditions.

The above mentioned entities will act, as the case may be, as data processors or persons in charge of the processing or as separate data controllers. In respect of the latter, the data will be communicated only with the express consent of the user, save for cases in which the communication is compulsory or necessary by the applicable law, or for purposes for which the applicable law does not require the user’s consent. 

Save for that provided above, no personal data of the users is disclosed to other companies. 

## COOKIES

The Data Controller uses cookies on the Website. Cookies are text files that a website sends to a user’s terminal and that allow the website’s owner to store some of the data transmitted by the user’s browser during internet access.

Cookies are used to perform computer authentication, to track sessions and to store specific information relating to the users that access to the server and, usually, they are present in the browser of each user in a huge number.

By using the cookies the website’s owner may, among other things, carry out an analysis of the habits of a particular user in order to adapt the services rendered by the website to his/her needs, or to facilitate him/her during the internet access (for instance, by storing the username of the user so that he/she does not have to retype them for every access to the website).

To find out more about the cookies the Data Controller uses and how to control them, please refer to the Cookies Policy. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Website.

## RIGHTS OF THE DATA SUBJECTS

The data subjects have the right to obtain, at any time, confirmation as to whether or not personal data exist and to be supplied with a description of the categories of data being processed, the personal data involved, the purpose of the processing and recipients to whom the person data is disclosed as well as to verify the accuracy or to update and rectify their personal date. 

In certain cases, the user also has the right to erase, anonymous or block their personal data as well as the right to object to the processing of personal data.

Any request should be addressed to Lucini & Lucini Communications Limited at 19 Fitzwilliam Place, Dublin 2, Ireland or by email to [privacy@lucinilucini.com](mailto:privacy@lucinilucini.com). Where a user requests details of personal data which the Data Controller holds about them the request must be made in writing to the above address or by email giving details with which the Data Controller can identify the user along with an administration fee of €6.35 (payable by cheque to “Lucini & Lucini Communications Limited”) or such other fee as prescribed under the applicable data protection legislation. 

A user’s request will be dealt with as soon as possible and will not take more than 40 days to process (or such other period as laid by the applicable law). 

However, it is possible for users to exercise the opt-out to the e-mail service by visiting /ching-oracle/user-management/, inserting the relevant password and pressing the “unsubscribe” button or by writing to the above address or emailing, [privacy@lucinilucini.com](mailto:privacy@lucinilucini.com).

## AMENDMENTS AND UPDATES TO THIS STATEMENT

This statement may be amended or simply updated, in whole or in part, by the Data Controller at any time - due, primarily, to legal developments – and without giving notice to the users, without prejudice to the commitment of the latter to periodically take view of such statement. Therefore, the Data Controller encourages users to review the privacy statement regularly for any changes and the Data Controller will use personal data in accordance with the privacy statement under which that personal data was collected.

## SALE OR MERGER

If the Website is sold to or merged with, or if the business of the Data Controller is sold to, merges with or enters a joint venture with another company not owned by it, users should expect that some or all of the personal data collected from the Website may be transferred to the buyer/surviving company. If so, the Data Controller will seek to obligate the other company to use any personal data transferred by the Website in a manner consistent with this Policy, but the Data Controller cannot guarantee that it will be able to impose that requirement or that the acquiring company will comply.
